## **NEIL ORIBELLO**

#### • DETAILS •

14981 95a Ave, Surrey, V3R 7T6, Canada 7782236406 neil.oribello@gmail.com

#### • LINKS •

neoribello.github.io/portfolio/

## PROFILE

Passionate and enthusiastic Front End Developer with 1+ years of experience designing and building websites in the Real Estate industry. Proficient with HTML, CSS(SASS and POSTCSS), JavaScript and JS Frameworks, with knowledge of User Interface and Experience Design.

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Web Designer at Real Estate Webmasters, Vancouver

March 2019 — March 2020

- Web Designer at Real Estate Webmasters a web technology provider for the top 1% of real estate professionals in North America.
- Translates mock ups into front end components. The languages that were mainly used in my tenure: HTML, SASS, POSTCSS, JavaScript, Vue.js
- Designs web layouts for the clients using the Adobe Creative Cloud.
- Communicates with clients directly with regard to design, preferences, changes and deadlines.
- Collaborates with internal teams.e.g. quality, sales, other developer, designer and project manager for the completion of projects
- · Consistently meets deadlines and positive feedback from customers and team members

## Web Developer Intern at Cucumber Marketing, Vancouver

August 2017 — October 2017

• Student Intern - Redesigning web pages through WordPress

## EDUCATION

## Digital Design and Development Diploma, British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver

September 2018 — June 2019

· Graduated with distinction in my class

# New Media Design and Web Development Certificate, British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver

September 2016 — September 2017

• Graduated with distinction in my class

## ★ PROJECTS

#### Personal Portfolio

- Developed a personal project on Gatsby and Strapi
- Implemented a headless CMS (Strapi) where I consume API using GraphQL

#### **Shopify Ecommerce Project**

- Quarantine project where I started learning Shopify
- Built based on React where I picked a inspiration site to base styles off

#### Cart function project

- Cart function where items can be added, deleted or totaled.
- Shows a C.R.U.D system

## **¶** REFERENCES

#### Miranda Johnsen from Real Estate Webmasters

miranda.johnsen@gmail.com

### William Xu from DDS Wireless

williamwlxu@gmail.com · 7783193063

### **Christopher Manning from Bounteous**

christopherjmanning@gmail.com·+1-780-232-5301

## Kashmira Gadgil

gadgilka@gmail.com